[{"answer": "Because you need one. Besides, there's a girl you gotta meet", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Beautiful, you'll like he", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What is that shit? You spent 6 years bouncing from one dea", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You are back in the game! Convince me you belong here", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "--Watch out, my friend, he's a fixer", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Did you call home? Let 'em know how you did? How you're doing", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I just want to get to know you", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I want to get into your mind, your heart, your soul. I don't see you wearing any pants in this equation", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Nothing, I just don't talk like that", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It's not that I can't. Why do I have to", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "... What'd you just say", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, you said", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "A knock would be nice, my friend", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'll rush right over. Stat", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Inside? I've got nothing inside", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend's leading", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hold on, my friend, if I didn't block his calls would you've talked to him? Honestly", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Then what exactly is the point, my friend? What's the full story here? What's the deal with your old man", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Save your strength. Help's coming. Help's coming", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Of course I do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Pick one", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'll do your job tomorrow, today you do mine", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're working out of my shop", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Really? Is that what you were thinking", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Really? Is that what you were thinking", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Nice job, now don't blow it by getting ahead of yourself. I'm looking beyond the money", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "... How do you go 3 and 11? Wanna know how", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Fuck Monday night! Fuck the parlay", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You'd bet your mother's house on it", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "If you did", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Just like that? No goodbye", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I'm sure it is... I wonder what's not in here", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm sure it is... I wonder what's not in here", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What do you mean, what do I mean? When it comes to my friend you seem to have all the answers", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You have no idea, huh", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No I'm not. This is the game", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Do you deny it", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I know you did", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Don't make this about me", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah, I put the tray out there", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Where are you headed", "docId": "Two-For-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Does your mom know I'm in rehab", "qsentId": 46}]